Guide to the Medical Center Public Relations records, 1913-1999 RG0045
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Burns Clinic Photographs, 1913-1981; RG0045 Series 8; 5 Linear feet (Box 4, Box 3, Box 2, Box 1, Box 8, Box 7, Box 6, Box 5, Box 10, Box 9)
  - Alumni Weekend, Opthamology post-graduate course [1/2], 05/1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Prints, negatives, and articles - "Alumni PG Course a Real Eyeful" and "Madden, Zimmerman '68 Alumni Awards." Also, Scientific Assembly, May 24,1968 (programs, articles, correspondence, Military Medicine Today Abstract, brief abstracts for publication, Is It really a Stroke? etc. Also Alumni weekend and Ob-Gyn post-graduate course, May 1969
  - Alumni Weekend, Opthamology post-graduate course [2/2], 05/1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Anasthesia Patents, 1847-1931 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes, correspondence about Morton inhaler, and rules books on patents
  - Bryner Twins, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Balding, Lynn, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Includes infusion notes
  - Beaumont Society research day, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Includes Dr. Canter's gift painting to the university
  - Burditt Nurses, 03/21/1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cancer Clinic, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Christmas, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Contact sheets [1/2], undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Miscellaneous
  - Contact sheets [2/2], undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Dedication and Commencement, 07/1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Negatives
  - Department of Medicine, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Prints and notes
  - EMI press conference, 11/08/1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Prints, negatives, and contact sheets (original finding aid does not explain EMI)
  - Eugene Meyer Pavilion groundbreaking and dedication [1/3], 06/1964 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Prints and contact sheets
  - Eugene Meyer Pavilion groundbreaking and dedication [2/3], 06/1964 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Eugene Meyer Pavilion groundbreaking and dedication [3/3], 06/1964 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Eugene Meyer Pavilion dedication, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Prints, negatives, and contact sheets
  - Fellows, Macy, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Footer, David; Louis Laroache; David Curfman; and Sue Banen, 04/1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - GWU Medicine, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Head-shots and board meeting, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Heart disease, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Hospital: Administration Program Building, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Prints and article "Executive Suite"
  - Hospital: Admitting office, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Hospital: Anesthesiology, 06/1958 --07/1958 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Hospital: Blood Bank, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Hospital: Christmas, December 1958 and 1959, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Hospital: Conference Room, 02/1951 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Hospital: Dietary, 1948-1961 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Hospital: Disaster alert drill, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Hospital: Emergency room, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Hospital: Equipment, 1958-1960 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Prints and negatives
  - Hospital: Exteriors, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Includes a twilight shot of the capital from the dean's office
  - Hospital: Father's lounge, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Hospital: Floor plan, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Hospital: Gifts, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Hospital: Harry F. Duncan Pavilion, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Prints and contact sheet
  - Hospital: Heart Station and Guild Yearbook, 1958-1963 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Hospital: Heart Surgery, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Original finding aid includes "?," so the file may not pertain to heart surgery
  - Hospital: Inspection, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Hospital: Intensive Care, 1956-1960 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Hospital: Various internal and external prints, 1947-1964 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Hospital: Various internal and external prints, 1967-1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Includes Hospital's Nineteenth birthday, small pox vaccination, slides, negatives, contact sheets, and article "Physicians to Work in Groups"
  - Hospital: Laboratories, 1955-1959 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Hospital: Laundry, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Hospital: Maternity Department and pregnancy, 1948-1963 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Hospital: Medical records, 1949-1966 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Prints and correspondence
  - Hospital: Miscellaneous, 1941-1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Prints include picture of President Trachtenberg, negatives, contact sheets
  - Hospital: Neurology, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Hospital: Nurses Home, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Everglades Hall
  - Hospital: Opening, 1913-1967 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Includes prints, information, notes, correspondence, letters, newspaper clippings, articles, and commencement program
  - Hospital: Orthopedics, 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Includes football picture of Andy Davis, who had an excision of knee cartilage in Spring of 1949
  - Hospital: Outpatient Department, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Hospital: Pathology, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Hospital: Patients, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Hospital: Plastic surgery, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Hospital: Radiology department, 1948-1958 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Hospital: Safety, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Hospital: Service Awards, 05/16/1967 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Prints and program
  - Hospital: Solarium 6-A, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Prints, negatives, and picture release forms
  - Hospital: Surgery department, 1948-1961 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Prints, contact sheets, and picture release forms
  - Hospital: Surgery department, 1949-1952 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Hospital: Twins, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Hospital: University Clinic, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Prints and part of an article
  - Hospital week, 05/16/1969 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Hospital: Women's board, 1964-1972 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Prints and news release forms
  - Insulin Infusion, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Negatives and slides
  - Inter-negatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Internships and intern resident matching day, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Prints, negatives, contact sheets, and a short article
  - Internships, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Jerri, Wendell, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Also includes open house for day treatment program (April 1986)
  - Keshishian, John, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Prints and biographical sketch
  - KI--Wives scholarship luncheon, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Negatives and contact prints only
  - King, Kane, 03/15/1973 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Kostecki, Colonel Walter--Fort Myer Post, 06/12/1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    News release
  - Le Barons--Dr. Parks, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Library, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Linen Accelerator, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Linen service, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Lorenz, Dr. and Brian Zimmermans; Marin Footer and Betty McKee in Medical School, 03/1973 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Low vision children and Dr. Roberts Sunga, 04/1973 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Low vision clinic, 09/1971 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Includes correspondence, news releases, and articles
  - Ludewig--Hospital Administrator, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Includes GW Friday Report bulletin
  - Marymount girls, 03/1970 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Article "Nurse Fledglings"
  - Matching Day, 1970-1983 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - McCarthy, Kenneth: Candidate for MS in Biochemistry, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Correspondence
  - McClaren, John: Public Information Fellow at GW Medical Center, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Mead, Johnson: Collector of Pediatric antiques, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Program and inventory
  - Medical Center, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Medical functions, laboratory, and central monitoring, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Medical School: Bacteriology, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Medical School, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Medical School: Catalogue prints, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Medical School: Construction and contract signing, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Medical School: Department of Anatomy, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Medical School: Exterior shots, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Medical School: Heart research, 1953-1956 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Medical School: Miscellaneous, 1930-1966 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Medical School: Orientation, 09/1972 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Medical School: Pharmacology department, 1951-1958 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Medical School: Staff and students, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Medical society, 10/1965 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Medicare signing, 05/1966 --06/1966 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Medicine: Space Medicine, 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Medidata signing, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Merrill Trust: Kenneth Crosby and Dean Parks, 04/1966 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Metro: Foggy Bottom--GWU opening, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Negatives, contact prints, slides
  - Miscellaneous, 1948-1989 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Includes graphs and correspondence
  - Miscellaneous medical notes, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous hospital scenes, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
    Includes nurses show, caesarian seciton, birthing, Dr. Samuel Loube, Dr. Alec Horwitz, surger, ER, varioius doctors, boiler room, kitchen
  - Mullins Christmas tree for birds, 12/1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Multiphase health screening, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Prints, contact sheets, and negatives
  - Navy--GWU programs and navy-hospital signing, 03/1972 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Contact sheets and negatives
  - News: Medical, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Prints, newspaper articles, and correspondence
  - Nursery Show awards, 02/1973 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Prints and contact sheets; includes Dr. Adkins performing surgery because of emergency blood clot in lung
  - Nurses and medical faculty, 1913 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Nursing department, 1950-1981 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Nursing department, 1948-1950 -- --ca. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Open house clinic naming and sesquicentennial site dedication [1/2], 02/1971 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Open house clinic naming and sesquicentennial site dedication [2/2], 02/1971 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Open house clinic naming and sesquicentennial site dedication [1/2], 02/1971 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Open house clinic naming and sesquicentennial site dedication [2/2], 02/1971 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Prints, negatives, contact sheets, slides, notes, article
  - Opening Assembly, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Opening Assembly and orientation, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Includes program, notes, news release, and article "New Horizons for Medicine"
  - Opening Assembly, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Opening Assembly, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Includes program and short article
  - Opening Assembly, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Prints, negatives, contact sheets
  - Opening Assembly, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Opening Assembly, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Prints, negatives, contact sheets, news release, excerpts, Dean's speech, and article "A Challenge for Tomorrow"
  - Opthamology, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Orientation, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Orientation, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Includes program
  - Postgraduate seminar drawing, 05/1973 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Retirement parties, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Dr. Ludewig (6/29/1973), Miss Elizabeth Young (7/18/1973), Dr. Allan Weingold and Dr. Derrick (6/27/73)
  - Service awards dinner, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Slides: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Social gatherings and events, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Softball game and picnic, 09/1980 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Teaching [1/2], 1961-1966 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Teaching [2/2], 1961-1966 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Teaching, 1964-1988 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Prints, negatives, contact sheets, and slides
  - Teaching, 1961-1974 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Teaching, 1961-1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Terry the Torso, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Prints, negatives, and news releases
  - University Clinic, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Whitehead, Jay; Jeff Tarbert; Alvin Sanford, 02/1973 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Negatives and contact sheets
  - Witoelar, Suvatchara Ph.D. and Dr. Lightfoote with patient, 02/1973 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Negatives, prints, and contact sheets, the doctors are conducting neurological tests such as epilepsy
- Medical School faculty, 1950-1989; RG0045 Series 9; 1 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2)
  This series contains photographs. The material dates from 1950 through ca.1980. The subjects of these images are medical school faculty members. Some noteworthy individuals are Walter Bloedorn, Paul Carlson, Joseph Roe, and Joseph Sizoo.
  - Dr. Ralph G. Beachley, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dean Walter A. Bloedorn [1/7], 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2.1)
  - Dean Walter A. Bloedorn [2/7], 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2.2)
  - Dean Walter A. Bloedorn [3/7], 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2.3)
  - Dean Walter A. Bloedorn [4/7], 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2.4)
  - Dean Walter A. Bloedorn [5/7], 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2.5)
  - Dean Walter A. Bloedorn [6/7], 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2.6)
  - Dean Walter A. Bloedorn [7/7], 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2.7)
  - A woman and Dean Bloedorn in front of a painting, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2.8)
  - Dean Bloedorn with Dr.Marvin [1/2], 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2.9)
  - Dean Bloedorn with Dr. Marvin [2/2], 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2.1)
  - Dean Walter A. Bloedorn, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2.11)
  - George Washington University Hospital, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 2.12)
  - Dean Walter A. Bloedorn [1/2], 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2.13)
  - Dean Walter A. Bloedorn [2/2], 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2.14)
  - Photo of the Iron Lung, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2.15)
  - Dean Bloedorn & Dr. Danniel Seckinger, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2.16)
  - Dean Bloedorn & Dr.Carmichael And Dr. Virginia Duggins Photo, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.17)
  - Dean Bloedorn & Dr. Shannon, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 2.18)
  - Painting of Dean Walter A. Bloedorn, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.19)
  - Photo of Dr. Bloedorn and a woman in front of a painting of Dr. Bloedorn, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.2)
  - Daniel Leray Borden [1/5], 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3.1)
  - Daniel Leray Borden [2/5], 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3.2)
  - Daniel Leray Borden [3/5], 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3.3)
  - Daniel Leray Borden [4/5], 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3.4)
  - Daniel Leray Borden [5/5], 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3.5)
  - Photo of the faculty of the GWU School of Medicine, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.6)
  - Dr. William Ramsey, Dr Lloyd Elliott and Dr. Daniel L. Borden, 06/1966 (Box 1, Folder 3.7)
  - Daniel L. Borden, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.8)
  - Dr. Borden, Prof. Graighill, Dr. Sehrt, Dr. Dickens and Dr. Young, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.9)
  - Dr. Hunter, Dr. Borden, Dr. Gate and Prof. Choisser, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.1)
  - Dr. Borden, Dr. Cloyd H. Marvin and Dr. Herbert S. Gates, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.11)
  - William Cine Borden, undated (Box 1, Folder 4.1)
  - Photo of Borden General Hospital, undated (Box 1, Folder 4.2)
  - Alexand Breslow [1/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 5.1)
  - Alexand Breslow [2/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 5.2)
  - Dr. C.A. Cesar [1/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 6.1)
  - Dr. C.A. Cesar [2/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 6.2)
  - Dr. C.A. Cesar [3/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 6.3)
  - Dr. C.A. Cesar [4/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 6.4)
  - Dr. C.A. Cesar and Dr. Oscar B. Hunter Jr., undated (Box 1, Folder 6.5)
  - Missing, undated (Box 1, Folder 6.6)
  - Dr. C.A. Cesar, undated (Box 1, Folder 6.7)
  - Jay Barr, undated (Box 1, Folder 7.1)
  - Dr. Paul Carlson, Dr. Etherington and Philip Littleford on a medical missionary a Congo village [1/3], undated (Box 1, Folder 7.2)
  - Dr. Paul Carlson, Dr. Etherington and Philip Littleford on a medical missionary a Congo village [2/3], undated (Box 1, Folder 7.3)
  - Dr. Paul Carlson, Dr. Etherington and Philip Littleford on a medical missionary a Congo village [3/3], undated (Box 1, Folder 7.4)
  - Dr. Wu S. Chiu [1/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 8.1)
  - Dr. Wu S. Chiu [2/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 8.2)
  - Dr. Wu S. Chiu [3/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 8.3)
  - Dr. Wu S. Chiu [4/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 8.4)
  - Dr. Wu S. Chiu [5/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 8.5)
  - Dr. Wu S. Chiu [6/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 8.6)
  - Negative - Patricia A. Deboard, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Jerome Epstein [1/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 10.1)
  - Jerome Epstein [2/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 10.2)
  - Negative - Joseph Fridedman, M. D., undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Men and Women at a dinner party, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.1)
  - Men open wine at a party, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.2)
  - Unknown negative, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.3)
  - Dean Angus M. [1/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 12.4)
  - Dean Angus M. [2/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 12.5)
  - Dean Angus M. [3/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 12.6)
  - Dean Angus M. [4/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 12.7)
  - Dean Angus M. Griffin drinks, 09/1967 (Box 1, Folder 12.8)
  - Dean Angus M. Griffin and Frank Miller, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.9)
  - Dean Angus M. [1/7], undated (Box 1, Folder 12.1)
  - Dean Angus M. [2/7], undated (Box 1, Folder 12.11)
  - Dean Angus M. [3/7], undated (Box 1, Folder 12.12)
  - Dean Angus M. [4/7], undated (Box 1, Folder 12.13)
  - Dean Angus M. [5/7], undated (Box 1, Folder 12.14)
  - Dean Angus M. [6/7], undated (Box 1, Folder 12.15)
  - Dean Angus M. [7/7], undated (Box 1, Folder 12.16)
  - A man standing next to a painting - two copies, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.17)
  - A man standing next to a woman - two copies, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.18)
  - A group of people admiring a painting - two copies, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.19)
  - A group of people admiring a painting, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.2)
  - Two women and a man having a conversation, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.21)
  - A group of people admiring a portrait, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.22)
  - Two women and a man having a conversation, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.23)
  - Two women & a man admiring a portrait [1/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 12.24)
  - Two women & a man admiring a portrait [2/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 12.25)
  - Two women & a man admiring a portrait [3/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 12.26)
  - Two women & a man admiring a portrait [4/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 12.27)
  - Two women & a man admiring a portrait [5/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 12.28)
  - A man admiring a portrait, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.29)
  - People at a party admiring a portrait, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.3)
  - Dr. Michael Halberstam, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Negative - Roy C. Heflebower, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Dr. Alex Horiwitz [1/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 15.1)
  - Dr. Alex Horiwitz [2/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 15.2)
  - Dr. Alex Horiwitz [3/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 15.3)
  - Dr. Alex Horiwitz [4/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 15.4)
  - Dr. Alex Horiwitz [5/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 15.5)
  - Dr. Alex Horiwitz [6/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 15.6)
  - Dr. Alex Horiwitz [7/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 15.7)
  - Dr. Alex Horiwitz [8/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 15.8)
  - Dr. Alex Horiwitz [9/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 15.9)
  - Dr. Alex Horiwitz [10/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 15.1)
  - Dr. Alex Horiwitz [11/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 15.11)
  - Dr. George A. Kelser [1/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 16.1)
  - Dr. George A. Kelser [2/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 16.2)
  - Dr. George A. Kelser [3/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 16.3)
  - Dr. George A. Kelser [4/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 16.4)
  - Dr. George A. Kelser [5/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 16.5)
  - Dr. George A. Kelser [6/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 16.6)
  - Dr. George A. Kelser & Dr. James M. Bacos, undated (Box 1, Folder 16.7)
  - E. K. Morris, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Dr. Sean OReilly [1/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 18.1)
  - Dr. Sean OReilly [2/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 18.2)
  - Dr. LeLand W. Parr, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Drs. Alvin Parrish, Daniel Mazzuchi, Norman Kramer and Mrs. Evie Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Dr. Roe walking in the Joseph H. Roe room [1/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 21.1)
  - Dr. Roe walking in the Joseph H. Roe room [2/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 21.2)
  - Dr. Roe walking in the Joseph H. Roe room [3/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 21.3)
  - Dr. Roe walking in the Joseph H. Roe room [4/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 21.4)
  - Dr. Roe walking in the Joseph H. Roe room [5/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 21.5)
  - Dr. Roe walking in the Joseph H. Roe room [6/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 21.6)
  - Two men shaking hands, undated (Box 1, Folder 21.7)
  - Dr. Joseph H. Roe, 05/21/1953 (Box 1, Folder 21.8)
  - Dr. Joseph H. Roe, undated (Box 1, Folder 21.9)
  - Dr. Joseph H. Roe & Dr. Luther H. Snyder, 02/20/1954 (Box 1, Folder 21.1)
  - Dr. Joseph H. Roe [1/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 21.11)
  - Dr. Joseph H. Roe [2/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 21.12)
  - Dr. Joseph H. Roe [3/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 21.13)
  - Dr. Joseph H. Roe [4/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 21.14)
  - Dr. Joseph H. Roe [5/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 21.15)
  - Dr. Joseph H. Roe [6/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 21.16)
  - Photo and neg - Dr. Joseph H. Roe [1/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 21.17)
  - Photo and neg - Dr. Joseph H. Roe [2/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 21.18)
  - Photo and neg - Dr. Joseph H. Roe [3/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 21.19)
  - Photo and neg - Dr. Joseph H. Roe [4/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 21.2)
  - Photo of The Ernst Bischoff Award in Clinical Chemistry [1/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 21.21)
  - Photo of The Ernst Bischoff Award in Clinical Chemistry [2/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 21.22)
  - Dr. George B. Roth [1/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 22.1)
  - Dr. George B. Roth [2/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 22.2)
  - Dr. George B. Roth [3/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 22.3)
  - Dr. George B. Roth [4/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 22.4)
  - Dr. Joseph R. Sizoo, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Dr. William W. Stanbro, M.D. [1/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 24.1)
  - Dr. William W. Stanbro, M.D. [2/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 24.2)
  - Dr. William W. Stanbro, M.D. [3/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 24.3)
  - Dr. William W. Stanbro, M.D. [4/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 24.4)
  - Dr. William W. Stanbro, M.D. [5/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 24.5)
  - Myer H. Stoiar [1/3], undated (Box 1, Folder 25.1)
  - Myer H. Stoiar [2/3], undated (Box 1, Folder 25.2)
  - Myer H. Stoiar [3/3], undated (Box 1, Folder 25.3)
  - Dr. Howard Tickton [1/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 26.1)
  - Dr. Howard Tickton [2/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 26.2)
  - Dr. George V. Vahouny [1/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 27.1)
  - Dr. George V. Vahouny [2/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 27.2)
  - Dr. George V. Vahouny [3/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 27.3)
  - Dr. George V. Vahouny [4/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 27.4)
  - Dr. George V. Vahouny [5/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 27.5)
  - Dr. Mary F. Watt [1/14], undated (Box 1, Folder 28.1)
  - Dr. Mary F. Watt [2/14], undated (Box 1, Folder 28.2)
  - Dr. Mary F. Watt [3/14], undated (Box 1, Folder 28.3)
  - Dr. Mary F. Watt [4/14], undated (Box 1, Folder 28.4)
  - Dr. Mary F. Watt [5/14], undated (Box 1, Folder 28.5)
  - Dr. Mary F. Watt [6/14], undated (Box 1, Folder 28.6)
  - Dr. Mary F. Watt [7/14], undated (Box 1, Folder 28.7)
  - Dr. Mary F. Watt [8/14], undated (Box 1, Folder 28.8)
  - Dr. Mary F. Watt [9/14], undated (Box 1, Folder 28.9)
  - Dr. Mary F. Watt [10/14], undated (Box 1, Folder 28.1)
  - Dr. Mary F. Watt [11/14], undated (Box 1, Folder 28.11)
  - Dr. Mary F. Watt [12/14], undated (Box 1, Folder 28.12)
  - Dr. Mary F. Watt [13/14], undated (Box 1, Folder 28.13)
  - Dr. Mary F. Watt [14/14], undated (Box 1, Folder 28.14)
  - Charles S. White with two women, undated (Box 1, Folder 29.1)
  - Charles S. White with two men, undated (Box 1, Folder 29.2)
  - A series of photos of Charles S. White [2/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 29.3)
  - A series of photos of Charles S. White [1/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 29.4)
  - Charles S. White [1/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 29.5)
  - Charles S. White [2/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 29.6)